+91 7600-556-556



mihirrdave21@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/mihir-r-dave



SKILLS



WooCommerce

MySQL

jQuery

HTML

PHP

CSS

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Computer Engineering SVBIT - Gandhinagar | 2016 - 2019

Diploma in Computer EngineeringAMEC - Dhari | 2013 - 2016

Class X

VPG High School, GSEB

HOBBIES

Books Games Psychology Gym & Swimming Movies & TV Series Travelling & Stargazing

MIHIR DAVE

WordPress | WooCommerce | HTML | PHP | MySQL | jQuery | CSS

ABOUT ME

From my early days of writing simple programs to now leading the development of complex eCommerce solutions, my journey has been all about curiosity and constant learning. With 4.5 years of experience in WordPress and WooCommerce, I'm dedicated to building websites and stores that don't just work—they help my clients' businesses shine.

I love mentoring junior developers, sharing what I've learned, and keeping communication with clients smooth and easy every step of the way. Together, we create something amazing every time!

EXPERIENCE

Sr. Software Engineer [Oct 2023 - Present]

Shaligram Infotech LLP - Full-time

This past year at Shaligram, I've deepened my WordPress expertise as Associate Team Lead, delivering more customized projects.

Software Engineer [Oct 2019 - Sep 2023]

KudosIntech Software Private Limited - Full-time

In 3.5 years at Kudos, I've developed custom WordPress solutions, specializing Woocommerce, ACF Blocks, and payment gateway integration.

CAREER OBJECTIVE IN ONE QUOTE

Greatness comes from humble beginnings; it comes from grunt work. It means you're the least important person in the room—until you change that with results.

PROJECTS

In my journey as a WordPress developer, I've actively contributed to 75+ projects. Within this spectrum, I've performed various roles: acting as a dedicated developer for certain projects, playing a supportive role within a team for others, and overseeing the management of a few.

Here's the list of some of the great projects I've had the privilege to contribute to:

1) Africa Web Solutions

 This is the latest project I've been working on—a fully customized bus booking platform tailored for our client in Africa. We've transformed the traditional WooCommerce experience into a streamlined booking system using AJAX, custom SQL queries, and advanced session handling, along with key customizations to the WooCommerce modules.

2) Manhood Journey

- This site teaches a man how to become a better father. One of the best projects I've worked on.

 Pages are made through Avada Page Builder and mostly we have kept the default workflow for the woocommerce.
- But the real magic happens in the My Account module. The client wanted a custom my account module and it was a complex module so we used AJAX, Custom SQL queries, Woocommerce template customization, and all. I was working as a dedicated developer on that project and definitely learned a lot from that project.

3) Focus Waukesha

- This is the latest project we've been working on. This project is on a new level of custom WordPress development. The site is built with custom ACF blocks with customized woocommerce flow.
- This is one of that projects which keeps you up at night. we were three dedicated developers working really hard on this project. Again a project with a tight deadline. So definitely it improved my time management skills and I learned how you can work crazy long hours and still get excited to go to work again. Every day was a new journey and it was great!